{"data":[{"question":"The division between the roles of the mother and the father is no longer very clearly.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"person","b":"who","c":"for","d":"money","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Who-> whom","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"A father can change the baby, dressed the children or make the dinner.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"table","b":"manners","c":"is","d":"those","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"A father is the person who provides us for money to feed and clothe ourselves.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"All","b":"beautiful","c":"for","d":"enjoyment","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Beautiful-> beautifully","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"A dad is the person who you ask for pocket money.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"always","b":"crowd","c":"at","d":"asking","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Always is-> is always","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"The table manners you have in a restaurant is very different from those you have at home.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"China","b":"are","c":"for","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- China-> Chinese","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"All the parks are beautiful kept and are for the use and enjoyment of the people.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"who","c":"in","d":"to learn","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- In->to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"There always is nearly a crowd at the door of the theatre asking for returned tickets.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"ever","b":"into","c":"remembering","d":"off","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Remembering-> remember","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"China teams are famous for their skill in table tennis.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Many","b":"no","c":"furnitures","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Furnitures-> furniture","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"There was once a foreigner who went in England to learn English.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a","b":"of","c":"paintings","d":"walls","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Paintings-> painting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"},{"question":"Many houses have no other furnitures in their rooms.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"be","b":"seeing","c":"that","d":"no","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Seeing-> to see","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"22","type":"1"}]}